Hello,Didi?
你好, Didi?
This is Sharon Solaye at the Sheraton Boston.
这是Sharon Solaye  在Sheraton Boston.
I have a special request.
我有个特别的请求.
I wonder if I could come over and talk to you about it?
我想知道我能过来和你谈谈吗?
Great.
很棒.
So,let me get this straight.
So, 让我直说吧.
He doesn't want his regular suite at the hotel.
他不想要他酒店里的常规套房.
Right.It's too small for him this time.
Right. 这次他嫌太小了.
He wants to rent a house.
他想租一个房子.
Yes.He wants a house with a garden.
Yes. 他想要一个房子  带花园的.
With a garden.Why?
带花园的, 为什么?
And he wants a large kitchen,
并且他想要一个很大的厨房
living room,and dining room.
起居室, 和餐厅.
It has to have plenty of light,
它必须有充足的光线,
and central air conditioning.
和中央空调.
It must be near transportation,
它必须靠近交通,
shopping,and the river.
购物, 和河.
How many bedrooms?
多少间卧室?
Nine.
9间.
Did I hear you correctly?
我听的是对的吗?
Nine bedrooms?
9间卧室?
Who is this client,the Vienna Boy's Choir?
这个客人是谁, 维也纳少年合唱团(Vienna Boy's Choir)?
Maybe.He wants it for a song.
或许吧. 他说不要太贵.
Well,there is something in Boston that fits his needs.
Well, 在波士顿有个地方符合他的需求。
Great.
很棒.
Unfortunately,the mayor lives there.
不幸的是, 市长住在那儿.
Do you think he'd mind moving out for a month?
你觉得他会介意搬出去住一个月吗?